- Good morning.
- Hey all.
- Good morning, everyone.
- Good morning.
RYOPI (29)
BAR OWNER
KAZUMA (26)
PART-TIMER
You girls getting along?
Now that Mimi has joined.
MIMI (29)
HOSTESS
Are you worried?
You sleep well?
I was wandering around
in the middle of the night.
So you didn't sleep well.
I guess not.
I thought I slept a lot,
but it was only two hours.
You didn't sleep at all.
Good morning, students.
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
Today, you will go help
our local community again.
MARU (28)
HOST
- Here we go.
- It's gonna be hot.
However,
since it requires hard physical labor,
only the male members will be going.
- Really?
- Only the guys?
Good luck, guys.
What kind of physical labor? Fighting?
Look! That's awesome!
There are pigs, too.
Are there really?
- Good morning.
- Hello, sir!
- Thank you for having us.
- Welcome!
Let's get started
- Let's see, five people?
- There's five of us.
Please, take a look at this.
This here is what Igei Farm is all about.
- Okay.
- Thank you very much.
I can't read the kanji.
- Thanks again.
- Of course.
"Ogimi Village is suffering
from depopulation,
and many farmers are struggling
with a lack of successors and manpower."
Mr. Igei uses traditional farming methods
without pesticides
to grow vegetables and raise livestock.
Please help Mr. Igei.
Take time to learn
about the value of country life.
- Understood.
- Got it. A pleasure, Mr. Igei.
MR. IGEI
So today, here's what we'll do.
Have you seen this vegetable before?
- Yes.
- Celery.
Celery.
I'd like to ask for your help
with the harvest right away.
First, you'll be using a knife.
- Those knives look well used.
- Take one. Hold it for me.
- Yes, sir.
Oh! Big scary knife!
That's the last thing
he should be giving them.
- Yeah, keep that far away.
- Ah… no, no, no. I'm scared.
- You're dressed perfectly.
- Yes, sir.
- I'll do my best.
- You don't mind getting a bit dirty?
- No, we're all set.
- All right, let's get to it.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay.
- Look at this field.
- It's huge.
- Feels like summer.
- This field is massive.
It's amazing.
Don't break it apart.
I'm pretty good at this. See?
- Look at that!
- Nice.
Okay.
This work is no joke.
Wow.
First, we take off all the bad leaves.
The lower ones.
Okay.
- Nice.
- Don't throw them.
Be gentle.
Even when you grab them,
they'll break easily.
As for the rest, that's pig food.
- Got it.
- Yeah.
These things are huge!
It's hot. No wonder I'm sweating.
In Okinawa,
you can grow anything in winter.
Oh, really?
We grow a lot of crops
at this time of the year
and send them to the mainland.
Oh, they're working hard.
Right, right.
They always work really hard.
- They take it seriously.
- You've gotta hand it to them.
I've never worked
this hard before. Takes a lot.
It's tough. There are so many steps.
Right.
So this is farming, huh?
Crazy.
We should be grateful
every time we eat celery.
- That's right.
- Right?
What should we do next?
All right, next…
we'll feed this to the pigs.
Oh, I want to feed them.
I can't wait.
I've never done farm work
like this before. So easy.
- It's fun when we do it together.
- It's fun, isn't it?
- No doubt.
- Yeah, it is.
Okay, give it to them.
They need to grow big.
Here you go.
They eat a lot.
Wow, they're so eager.
- Thank you for the food.
- This is good. Thank you, sir.
- Tastes sweet!
- Yeah, it's really good.
It does.
We eat this, and it becomes our blood.
It becomes our flesh.
It becomes our energy.
That's why food is so important.
It's important.
GIRLS' BEDROOM
I wonder what kind
of physical work they're doing.
I wonder what it could be?
- Fixing machines?
- Maybe, making new parts or carrying them.
Oh, real men's work.
To all the female members…
What's going on?
…a transfer student is coming.
Oh, that's amazing!
Coming here?
Please change into your swimsuits,
and gather at the beach near the sauna.
- Right now?
- Hey, my makeup will come off.
Oh, really? No way.
- What?
- The guys don't know about this.
That's right.
What would you do if it's a huge letdown?
If it's someone like Kazuma.
Just kidding.
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
IN OKINAWA
RUGGED APPRENTICE TATTOO ARTIST
DRAWN TO TATTOOS' SEX APPEAL
KAZUMA
KABUKICHO HOST BOSS
WHO WANTS TO GET SERIOUS ABOUT LOVE
MARU
IBARAKI HOSTESS WITH A BIKE CREW
LOOKING FOR A HUSBAND
AYACHERU
GYARU HOSTESS FROM MIYAGI
A TSUNDERE WHO HATES TO LOSE
RINRIN
KITASHINCHI BAR OWNER
WHO'S ALL ABOUT THE VIBES
RYOPI
WILD OKINAWAN NAIL ARTIST
WITH A PHOENIX ON HER BACK
SARA
FUKUSHIMA HOSTESS
WHO CHARGES INTO LOVE HEAD-FIRST
SHARAN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
EDOGAWA RAPPER
SEEKING LOVE WITH HONOR
RUNE
KITASHINCHI'S NO.1 HOSTESS
BLEEDING BIG-SIS ENERGY
MIMI
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON LOVE
A transfer student?
I wonder what he's like.
Do you think he'll be
a tough guy or a clean-cut guy?
- I hope he's clean-cut.
- He'll be tough.
After getting Mimi,
we're bound to get a handsome guy next.
I can hear a jet ski.
- You're right.
- What?
Huh? Look out there!
- He's here!
- That's him!
Seriously?
He's coming on a jet ski? Awesome!
- He's going so fast.
- Is he allowed to go that fast?
That's a nice jet ski. It's all black.
- Is it expensive?
- I don't know. No idea.
- Aren't you curious?
- If you say it's the real deal.
If it's that nice,
I guess it's expensive, right?
Nice to meet you.
Hey, everyone. I'm the transfer student.
I guess starting today,
I'll be living with you all.
My name is Kenjiro Kamada.
- Ah, he's nice.
- Oh, he's nice!
He's cool!
Welcome.
- Nice to meet you.
My name is Kenjiro Kamada.
I'm 30 years old.
I run a construction company.
Everyone I know calls me Kamaken.
I do martial arts.
Specifically, underground martial arts.
I used to be a champion.
When I was in kindergarten,
I was quite timid.
I kind of had this desire to
become stronger.
So I started judo and wrestling.
From there, I was pretty much
always getting into fights.
In elementary, middle, and high school,
I was too much of a troublemaker.
The teachers were probably
always keeping an eye on me.
They were strict,
but only with me.
No-one else.
I didn't like how they treated me.
So, eventually I kneed my teacher
and got expelled.
I don't care if people already hit it off.
I'll go for the girl,
and if someone else wants to go
for the same girl too, that's fine.
If it comes to a fight, I won't lose.
I don't really lose.
Sorry, guys.
This is scary.
- We're off!
- Bye-bye!
Bye, babe!
Isn't it super pretty?
- It's pretty!
- Amazing right?
KAMAKEN (30)
SAITAMA - MMA FIGHTER
This is so great! It's fun.
It's so much fun. Let's go faster.
- Shall we?
- Let's go faster!
Oh, wow! That's amazing!
How terrifying.
- Full of energy, huh.
- They are!
This is fun!
Rinrin is having fun.
Okay.
We're not even here.
- This is nice.
- Did your heart stop?
- Of course, it did!
- I can tell by your face.
- Look at those cute dimples!
- That's so fast, it's crazy.
- We read you like book.
- You girls should try it too!
How old are you, Sharan?
I'm 21. Hey, do you do martial arts?
I do, I do.
Someone said,
"Oh, here comes a martial artist."
Oh, it's cold!
Wait! My face is a mess!
It's all wet!
Okay, let's go back for now.
Okay, thank you.
You all worked so hard.
So as a reward, let's have a barbecue.
Especially the meat, we started
with one animal from a culling effort,
and now we have about 50.
Boar-pig hybrids and wild boars.
Are these the ones you raised, Mr. Igei?
- Yes, these.
- Living creatures.
- Yes, we're eating living things.
- These were over there, right?
Exactly.
- But you know…
- Yes?
…we can't live
without eating living things.
- That's true.
- That's right.
No other animal eats
as many living things as humans.
The most important thing
is to eat with gratitude.
I'm really glad
that you all got to know about this.
It was really fulfilling for me.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you, sir. Can I have one?
- Yes.
- Can I eat it?
- I'm digging in!
- I'm so happy.
This looks delicious. Let's eat.
Wow, it's so tender and delicious.
- It's good, right?
- So good!
Mmm!
BRING ON LIFE
So, what's your type? Should I go first?
Okay.
Someone who's cheerful,
and has a strong sense of self.
- Mmm.
I'm all about cheerful girls.
I think that's my type.
My type is someone who's funny
and we can have fun together.
- Okay, right.
- Well, my type is…
- Like…
- Hmm?
Someone I can just be myself around.
I want to be able to fart
in front of each other.
Ah…
I guess I have to include that too.
It is nice to be with someone
you can just be yourself around.
You want to fart, right?
How do I put it?
Someone with strong principles?
Someone who sees things through to the end
once they've decided.
Someone who doesn't turn
a blind eye to things.
Ah…
We were talking about
how you must really be motivated
- since you're a transfer student.
- I did come here motivated.
It's my plan to go all out.
Give it what I've got,
with the girl I'm interested in.
I came here to make up for lost time.
Oh, I see.
It's definitely a transfer student.
- Right?
- That's what it is.
- I wonder what he's like?
- He's going to make a move, for sure.
Better get going, Maru.
I'm wondering
if I can get along with the guys.
Well, well, well, let's see.
- They're probably all Yankii, right?
- Right.
What if they pick a fight with me?
What would you do?
If they try it…
- I'll have to fight back.
- Oh?
Of course.
- We're back!
- Welcome back!
We brought celery!
Oh, I love celery!
- We picked some.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Are you the transfer student?
I'm Kamaken.
- Hamaken?
- Kamaken.
- How are you?
- Nice to meet you.
Good. They're playing nice.
- A tourist?
- I'm the transfer student.
- Tourist? That's hilarious.
- What's your name?
- I'm Kamaken.
- Kamaken?
Kamaken is very polite.
That's a fighter for you.
Nice to meet ya!
Here it comes.
And now, it's sauna time.
This time, the one
who can choose a partner is…
the transfer student, Kamaken.
What? Why?
Please switch with me.
Please choose a woman
you'd like to go to the sauna with.
You could choose a guy.
What should I do? Uh…
Who to pick?
- Mimi, do you want to go?
- Yes.
The rest of you,
use the one-on-one time
to get to know each other better.
Oh, I bet we can drink.
You can drink alcohol
during the one-one-one time.
- This is the best!
- That's all I need!
However, be careful do not drink too much.
Isn't it too early?
I don't need anything else anymore.
REFRESHED
- Whoa, Kamaken.
- Wow.
This isn't some kind
of foreign porno, right?
Hey.
- Whoa, it's hot.
- Yeah.
You're famous, right? Aren't you?
No, no, not at all.
Just in the normal world of hostess clubs.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Originally, I graduated and became
a nursery school teacher right away.
- Oh, that's amazing.
- Yeah.
But the pay was lower than what I made
at my part-time job in high school.
- Really?
- Yeah, so I thought, "This is bad."
The only time I could work was at night.
And that's how I came to do this work.
When COVID hit, I thought I would quit.
I wanted to become a nurse.
Wow, that's amazing.
Yeah. When I was thinking about
- quitting that job,
- That's great.
the owner of the hostess club
I worked at told me…
He said…
something like,
"You don't really leave an impression."
First I thought,
"Why would he say that to me?"
But after a little while,
I started to say,
- "Just wait until I get serious."
- Hmm.
Yeah, so that got me fired up
- and now I'm like this.
- Right.
Is anyone here your type?
You know, I'm still--
If we're talking about looks,
based on my first impression
of everyone here, you're my type.
- Really?
- At least in looks.
He's so straightforward.
But, I don't know. I don't really
look at faces and stuff like that.
- Mmm-hmm. For sure.
- But from first impressions,
I think Rune is like
a god to me right now.
- Oh, Rune? I see.
- Yeah.
Like, his personality
and face are cool, right?
- Well, I won't lose to him.
- Yeah.
I'm the oldest here. True.
- So, you know…
I can't lose to the young ones.
SAUNA
You're easy to talk to.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna go after you.
I think Kamaken is someone who expressed
his feelings very straightforward.
Honestly, I have very low confidence
in the way I look, my appearance,
and stuff like that.
And because I lack that confidence
I instead put a lot of effort
into my makeup.
I've also had a nose job
and all sorts of other things.
It's something that has become
a trauma for me.
I think my high school relationship
is what gave me that trauma.
I don't want to be
cheated on again in my life.
That's why I really care about
how the other person has lived their life.
I hope that as we continue,
I can hear more about that from him.
Since none of us know
how much longer we'll be here,
I want to make sure I make the most
of the time I have remaining here.
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
- I see.
- That's right.
Mimi has trauma from a past relationship.
That was unexpected.
She dated a senior at her part-time job
for four or five years
when she was in high school.
They had even promised to get married,
but she found out
that he was cheating on her.
Apparently, it was with a classmate.
- So, after beating him up…
- What?
she decided she doesn't like playboy types
who try to manipulate her with sweet talk.
- I see.
- Ah.
So we had Mimi and Kamaken's sauna.
He's a fighter, after all.
I guess he would go
straight for her at first. Probably.
And he doesn't have much time.
That's right. They have less time.
So, he has no choice but to go for it.
He made another flashy entrance.
- Really!
- Jet ski.
Was this the production's idea?
Um, that's something we agreed on.
- You agreed on that?
- We came to an agreement with Kamaken.
- Was he okay with it?
- He said "I prefer it that way."
- Do people ever really agree on a jet ski?
- That doesn't happen often.
It doesn't. Funny how people
actually agree on a jet ski entrance.
I was just grateful
that we both had the same idea.
I thought it was Dangerous Cops.
Can you pour me some tequila?
Yeah, here you go.
Haven't you been here too long?
It's crazy, right?
It's crazy.
They were great. I don't feel
the Part 1 members
were better than this group at all.
I liked them. We became friends.
I learned a lot
from being with the first group.
- Oh, really?
- I still think about them.
I see.
But I switched gears, so I'm here now.
Yeah, but I feel like,
"Is that really true?"
What do you mean?
You know, I can't trust people.
I have a personality where I doubt people.
Yeah, I think that's fine.
Because I guess, I really am gullible.
I really get influenced easily.
Like, one of the guys I met in Tokyo
used a fake name.
Seriously, that guy was nothing but lies.
Honestly…
How do I put it? I have trust issues.
I know it's not good
that I start doubting people.
It's a bad trait of mine.
Some of these things are a bit concerning.
Like what?
You said you're gullible,
easily influenced,
and quick to agree with other people.
I wonder if you can really be
in a relationship when you feel like that.
If it was in the past, it would be fine.
But you said you still
get influenced easily. That' a concern.
Mmm-hmm.
Right now…
I don't know who you like
or who you're interested in, you know?
Hmm.
Well, it's hard to say.
- Why is that?
- It's really…
- Just say it.
- No, it's really hard to say.
It's fine. Well, I won't feel hurt.
I'm already used to it.
Um…
I like Tai-chan.
Mmm.
Is he happy?
I wonder.
Tai-chan is kind of interested
in Mimi right now, right?
I might be happy to hear how you feel.
Mmm.
I've been wondering
who it was this whole time.
Is that so?
So the new transfer student came, right?
Mmm.
But I just was like…
It's Tai-chan for me.
Mmm.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
Want a selfie?
- Let's do it.
- Sure.
- Okay!
- It's happening!
- Whoa, are you drunk?
- I am drunk.
- You're drunk?
- Very.
I'm drunk, very drunk.
Hmm.
Tai-chan! Look where her boobs are!
Her boobs are in his face. Look!
Tai-chan!
Are you drunk?
I'm drunk, very drunk.
I'm drunk, too.
I've been working on the railroad
- I'm so drunk.
- All the live long day
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
- Sorry for the wait.
- Thank you.
Hmm…
So, I've got this thing
about my personality.
There's a period
before you start dating, right?
Mmm.
If I have a bad experience
during that period,
I really lose interest.
Okay, I see.
Well, I take it
you don't really like Mimi.
- Mmm.
- I can tell just by looking.
This is cause I talk to her, right?
You can't stand me talking to her?
I wouldn't say I can't stand it.
I don't mind you talking to her.
But I don't want to see it
right in front of me.
So now I'm starting
to lose track of my own feelings.
Mmm.
Well,
I get how you feel,
but it's also the environment we're in.
Which is why I said it's fine.
What you do is up to you.
This isn't good.
This place is great!
BUDDHA LEAN
Are the seats assigned?
Just sit wherever you like.
The seats are different every day.
They change every day.
So Tai-chan really wants
to sit there after all!
- Then I'll sit on my knees.
- Why not here?
All right.
I'm having so much fun today.
- Already?
- I'm having so much fun.
It's so fun here.
I'm looking forward
to talking with the guys
just as much as I am with the girls.
- Yeah?
- Is that so?
That's why, if we do have a fight,
I want things to be good with us.
- You like to drink with the guys.
- I love drinking with the guys.
I had friends over all the time.
My place was a hangout spot.
I was always the host.
I see.
Even if we'd fought at first,
we could still be talking like this now.
It's not good to hold a grudge.
- True.
- Just settle it.
It would've been fine if we clashed.
Because I was confident
that we'd become friends afterward.
All the guys are good guys.
I don't know. It's like,
let's say Ryopi and I started dating.
I don't need to meet his female friends.
You mentioned that.
I don't want to see him
being friendly with other girls.
That's when Mimi came in and…
you two were talking.
- I mean, you're friends.
- Mmm-hmm.
I understand that,
but I don't want to see it in front of me.
For Ryopi, I know he can't ignore you.
I mean, I understand that.
- I know it's not your fault, Mimi.
- I get that.
I get it, but still,
I'm just saying, in life,
you're going to meet people
who run businesses and people who work.
I know that,
but I don't want to see it in front of me.
So, I'm rooting for him
when it comes to work.
On the other hand, I'm also a hostess,
so I also have opportunities
to talk to men,
I understand that.
But even though you say you understand,
I don't think you really do.
Really? I do understand, though.
I see work as work,
and love as love, okay?
- No, you don't.
- Huh? I do. I'm being serious.
I'm not lying.
No, you're 20 now, right?
The world you see at 20 is only this big.
Wow, that's amazing!
You just don't understand it.
I can tell you want to understand
but you can't. Honestly.
I'm sorry,
but I don't think you understand.
You're 20. We're 29.
- Wow, crazy.
- This has gotten pretty intense.
What's going on here?
If I came home and saw
that look in her eyes,
- I'd close the door.
- You would close it, right?
It's true that Rinrin has been
acting difficult for a while.
And it seems like she's starting
to lose track of her feelings.
Yeah, so this feels like
Mimi had no choice but to speak up.
Yeah, it was too much.
- That's right.
- She kept going on and on about it.
- Someone had to say it.
- Someone had to.
I guess you're right.
Maybe she simply can't separate
this current situation
from her past trauma.
Maybe she's getting flashbacks
of various things, probably.
- I see.
- The closer they get.
But that's a separate issue
from this relationship.
- Well, that's true.
- Right?
- This was something, huh?
- Really.
The world you see at 20.
This is just Buddha.
Buddha? Reclining Buddha?
- It's Buddha vibes.
- It's this, right? This is indeed Buddha.
- It's Buddha.
- I see it.
She's even dressed
kind of like Buddha, right?
In fact, her expression is similar too.
Ayacheru is the most drama-free.
She really is.
That little voice.
- That's not what she sounds like.
- She doesn't sound like that.
Doesn't she? Like a calf somehow…
- She's not a calf.
- She's the only one.
- You're exactly right.
- She's truly like water in a desert.
Truly like an oasis. Honest water.
Honest water.
- Okay.
- More basketball you hate.
Yeah, there it is.
- Like in prison.
- Like local delinquents.
Right, exactly.
Nice!
Kamaken is really good.
LIVING ROOM
- Yo.
- What the heck's this?
Morning.
When'd you go to bed?
You know how you said
you were drunk last night?
Is that the only reason
you said that stuff to me?
That's a secret.
What do you mean?
The weather is nice today,
so we will have a barbecue at the beach.
Since it is a barbecue,
alcohol will be allowed.
Everyone, please get ready.
Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Let's get to it, everyone!
Let's do this thing!
Wow, this is such a gorgeous view.
Okinawa is the best.
Badly in Love!
The greatest show!
With the greatest cast!
These 11 people
will drink best champagne…
and the best rosé! Here we go!
Three, two, one.
All right!
- Thank you! Here you go.
- Cheers!
Cheers!
Let's have fun!
Wow, this must be so much fun.
I'm gonna dump this on you.
So good!
- Here, here.
- Thanks.
Now, both of you.
Ready, set…
Go for it!
- What was that?
- Last longer than that.
Wow, incredible!
- You're so strong.
- Did you see that?
- He's strong!
- Very impressive.
The winner is Kamaken!
Come on, let's go again!
Knocked him over.
That shocked me just now!
Come at me, Kazuma!
All right, let's start this round fresh!
Ready, set. Let's go!
That's good.
Oh no, that spot's not great.
- Whoa!
- You can do it!
- Oh, no! Come on, come on!
- You're so strong.
- I couldn't do anything.
- Impressive.
Insane!
Now it's time for Ryupi to play.
Come on. Get out there!
- Come on, Ryupi, it's your turn now.
- Who the heck is Ryupi?
No, I only fight people I can beat.
And since Maru isn't here, I forfeit!
Wait, hold on. Just go once.
- Kamaken!
- Ryopi! Ryopi!
Hey, Sara, let's talk.
Sure.
I'm super frustrated.
You picked the wrong fight.
You definitely picked the wrong fight.
But I really thought I could win.
Well, it's not like you can beat everyone.
But, you know, I weigh more than him.
Yeah, that's true.
When someone's that heavy,
sweep their leg and it's over.
How do you know?
I've done MMA, judo, kickboxing as well.
- I didn't know that. You've done a lot.
- Yeah, I've also done Muay Thai.
- You're stronger than me!
- I probably wouldn't lose.
- Should we have a sumo match?
- I won't lose.
That would be fun for me.
I've been wanting to talk about tattoos
with you for a while. Can we?
He's finally getting to see her tattoos.
These cherry blossoms
were originally pink, right?
The cherry blossoms on top were pink.
- Wow.
- And yeah, I had those redone.
A Western tattoo artist did it,
so it ended up really colorful.
Oh, so this is one large
back tattoo, and the artist was--
- It was two.
- Oh, two artists.
Yeah, I had it done first in Okinawa.
Then, I asked someone
in Nara to work on me,
and I went over there to have them do it.
But you can't finish it in one go, right?
You had to go back?
Yeah, I took two overnight trips.
So, like, ten hours in two days.
- Seriously?
- That's right.
Wow, that's incredible.
Ten hours in two days?
I was shaking.
I was wondering
why I was paying to hurt so bad.
But you don't regret it?
No, I don't regret it.
But, you know, I'll probably regret it
when I have kids in the future.
- Mmm.
- I'm sure.
- You didn't get the eye of the phoenix?
- No.
Well, if there's ever
a good time to do it,
I'll probably add that part then.
It's about timing? Well, if I became
a tattoo artist by then, can I do it?
I'll consider it.
This is nice, huh?
- I haven't been on a swing in forever.
- Yeah, it's great here.
- It's hard to know you like someone.
- It's really hard.
To tell you straight, I can't tell.
Can you tell me what she just said?
I only caught the
"To tell you straight" part.
"To tell you straight, I can't tell."
You haven't figured it out?
- I haven't.
- What? You don't know, huh?
- That's not quite it.
- You're feeling unsure?
What are you actually feeling, then?
I'm curious to know
what you're actually feeling.
Oh, about who?
About me.
Wait, so for me, there was a part of me
that was always having doubt.
About what?
Well, so, um,
to tell you straight, I figured
you just found me easy to talk to.
And I figured that you didn't have any
true romantic feelings for me or anything.
I thought you probably just found me
easy to talk to, and that's all.
- You thought so?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Well, it's been about a week now,
- Yeah.
and, well, the person I like the most
at this stage hasn't changed.
It's still you, Aya.
Well, you know,
after talking to you today,
I do think it's you.
That you're the one I like the most.
Maybe… yeah.
- Awkward!
- Okay, let's get that in writing.
It's embarrassing to say this stuff.
She's so adorable.
It is, isn't it?
- Yes, it's embarrassing.
- But, I'm happy to hear it.
Well, the thing I like about her is…
it's really like,
I feel comfortable with her.
It's like we're on the same wavelength,
and I feel at ease
when I'm talking to her.
There are also parts of her
that I think are cute, yeah.
As for Mimi…
she has qualities that are attractive.
Of course, her looks, but also,
I'm interested in her
because we have things in common.
It's difficult.
I guess I'm being indecisive,
but that's my honest feeling right now.
- Cheers!
- How many have you had?
- What do you like to do? Tell me, Mimi?
- Songs, you mean?
Songs, hobbies, whatever.
I like saunas.
Oh, interesting.
You don't watch sports or anything either?
Well, I've been to a soccer game
and a baseball game before.
- Yeah, so…
- Did you play any sports?
Let's see, um… I played tennis.
Wow! What a blatant move!
- What a bold move.
- It is bold.
I wasn't really allowed to join clubs,
so there's that, but…
Oh, right. You did mention that.
But, I mean,
I have played a lot of different sports.
Mmm.
I've done a little bit of motocross too.
- I mean, yeah. that's cool. You know…
- Thanks.
- Is this everyone's?
- Save it for later.
- Eat up.
- Oh, thank you.
- How many?
- I'll take one.
- Here you go.
- Take a couple.
Eat up.
Sharan, wanna drink champagne?
- Pour me some.
- I'll take some.
You can have a little.
She's a lightweight.
- She's so cute.
- You good, Mimi?
That's amazing for a girl.
I want lemon.
Everyone's drinking to get drunk.
Sharan, let's drink.
You're pissing me off.
I mean, that's fine.
- We're at the beach!
- Okay.
I'm tipsy.
It's like,
he already knows that I like him,
so he went to another girl on purpose.
He's like, trying to make me jealous.
Kind of like, keeping me
as a backup, deliberately.
So, him playing around just pissed me off.
Let's toast.
Cheers.
To tell you a little bit about myself,
I was chosen as the 25th Junon Superboy.
Wow, that's amazing!
Yeah, I was bursting with youth!
My skin was porcelain,
and my hair was long and black.
I want to see that!
Wait, do you have it somewhere?
- Oh, I do. I'll show you sometime.
- Wow, I can't believe…
- I want to see! That's amazing!
- Yeah.
Then for about a year and a half,
I auditioned for a lot of different
TV shows and commercials and stuff, but…
I kept getting rejected
for a year and a half.
Even though I was being told
that I was the best-looking guy
in my hometown.
So when people keep telling you
that kind of thing,
do you naturally believe them?
To be 100% honest,
out of all the guys
in this school right now,
I think I'm the best-looking one.
My high-bridged nose, my big eyes,
my well-balanced features.
That's something a hostess would say.
Then also, my clear skin,
and my white teeth.
Because of that…
I think I'm number one.
So I have confidence in myself.
But, back in the day,
I kept getting rejected for a long time.
I ended up losing
confidence in myself at that point.
So then, I kept on getting rejected.
While that was going on,
I became a Kamen Rider
in Kamen Rider Ghost.
- Wow!
- I was on the hero side.
That's amazing.
I was about to say this
and made myself laugh, but…
I think of you as my Kamen Rider.
You mean that?
It's just at that moment,
I really saw you that way.
I guess, I'm saying you're really amazing.
Honestly, your looks,
your tattoos up to here,
at first I thought,
"Oh, this guy's bad news."
I thought you were probably
a really dangerous guy, but…
You have so much integrity.
Everything you say is inspiring.
And I really take into account
how people look.
I'm really not great with people
who seem flashy
or seem like
they're going to cause trouble.
So why did you want to do hip-hop,
and why did you get tattoos up to here?
I've been told from people around me
that when I have kids, for example,
that I won't be able to take them
to the pool or to hot springs and stuff.
That's what people have told me.
But if I can't go to the pool,
then I'll just build a pool at home.
Wow! Rune, you're so cool.
If I can't go to a hot spring,
I'll just rent the whole place.
Wow! Rune, you're so cool.
- Yeah, so like…
- Well, you know, it's true.
If you live an ordinary life,
you can't do that stuff,
but I don't intend to live
an ordinary life anyway.
I live the way I think is right,
but I don't think
that should cause trouble for others.
So, I wouldn't go out of my way
to show off my tattoos
at places that don't allow them.
You're a real-life Kamen Rider.
You do what you gotta do.
You guys still talking?
- Oh, no!
- What?
Stay away from here!
- Tai-chan.
- Just leave it. You don't stand a chance!
Oh, Tai-chan is so red
we can't see his "beauty" tattoo.
Oh! Hey.
- Cheers.
- Oh.
- You're a lightweight.
I'm just pretending to be.
You're just pretending?
Oh, you know, earlier,
when we were talking and stuff,
Sharan suddenly said to me,
like, "You're pissing me off."
But, it's like,
I'm not doing anything wrong.
The thing is, there's a big part of me
that wants to talk to you as well.
You wanted to get to know me too, right?
So, during this barbecue and stuff,
I'm not gonna focus solely on Sharan.
I also have a lot of desire
to talk to you, so…
When we're all chatting,
you want to talk to everyone
I mean, I think it's really nice
to have one-on-one chats too, but…
You want everyone to see you.
- Right? You're here for both parts. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Wait, but you're 22, aren't you?
You're turning 23 this year?
I'm 22.
Wait, you do turn 23 this year.
What do you think of a girl
who's 30 years old?
She's chatting to him
like he's a customer.
Like he's a customer.
I don't think it has
any bearing whatsoever.
Once you start dating,
you'll be on equal footing, right?
You should respect
the other person's opinions.
It's important to voice opinions
to each other.
It's not like, you know,
because there's an age gap,
that I want to be clingy or I want you
to spoil me, or anything like that.
I want us to face each other
on equal footing.
Tai-chan, how do I put this?
You speak beyond your years.
- I do?
- Yeah.
You think so?
Your face is exactly my type.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- The left side, I mean.
I don't know where to look, though.
Hey, Tai-chan.
- Oh my god!
- Let's talk.
Is there another barbecue
as chaotic as this one in the whole world?
- Sure.
- This is seriously gross.
No, it's gross.
- What is?
- It's super gross.
So, what is?
Well…
It's just blatant.
- Me?
- Yeah.
You go to her on purpose
the moment I said I don't like her?
- What did I do?
- You went after her.
This is seriously so annoying.
I'm so irritated. Really.
Why?
What were you talking about with her?
About me, right?
It's not that.
We were talking about
what I learned in Part 1 and stuff.
Was that all?
Mimi and I also talked
about romantic interests and other things.
I don't understand you, Tai-chan.
I don't understand you.
I don't get how you are either.
It is not my fault. So why blame me?
I feel like
we are misunderstanding each other.
I hate women like her.
Then, I just think
you should say that to her directly.
I mean, when you say that stuff to me,
it's not like I can do anything about it.
No, it's just blatant.
You two chatting like that.
Watching it, it's just gross.
I don't understand
why you're directing your anger toward me.
It really pisses me off.
Who's pissing you off? Mimi?
No, you.
I'm saying, I don't understand why--
Because I get jealous, okay?
- Interesting.
- And there it is.
That last "I get jealous" bit
was good, wasn't it?
Good, yeah. I thought it was endearing.
So, why did Mimi say
that his face was her type?
I think she's just looking at him
like he's her customer.
- I mean, it was completely different.
- I know, right?
Compared to Rune.
She was so animated
in that conversation with Rune.
And then, everyone's favorite, Ayacheru.
Ayacheru is really adorable.
To tell you straight, she's adorable.
Tell-it-straight Ayacheru.
She's adorable, isn't she?
To tell you straight, she's adorable.
Adorable.
Things seem to be going well between them,
but I can't figure Maru out.
I feel like the habits he picked up from
his job have something to do with that.
Because he's seen everything about women.
Between Mimi,
who has a bit of a darker side,
and Ayacheru,
who is innocent and carefree.
Maybe he's drawn to both of them.
I see.
Now that we've come this far,
there are no more fights,
and finally, the dating has begun.
Romance has begun. Yes.
The time to learn Ethics
and the time for violence is over.
It's finally starting from here.
The cast is complete.
- You are indeed correct.
- I couldn't be happier.
Sorry, Kazuma.
I'm gonna borrow Sara for a bit.
Don't you be chatting too long.
Let's drink this together. Let's share it.
Damn it!
You won't land one!
- Kamaken actually seems nice.
- Super good guy.
- They're both good guys.
- Both.
Wanna go in the water? We're here.
- Should we? You think?
- Let's.
After you.
Aah!
Oh god, it's cold.
Over here. It's a bit warmer.
He's like, "Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You didn't tell me you were swimming."
Kazuma!
Oh, Kazuma is coming. I'm scared, run!
- He's so scary!
- "I'm coming too!"
They're all scary, sort of.
- Here he comes!
- What do you think you're doing?
I'm scared, I'm scared!
Get over here, Kazuma!
I've been waiting for you!
This is way too deep!
- Hey, guys!
- You're crazy!
It's freezing in here!
You were taking too long, damn it!
Damn it! Why won't you go under?
- You guys are gonna drown!
- Okay, okay, okay!
He's gonna drown! No!
Come on! He'll drown.
Kazuma, let's talk over there.
- The two of us? Sure.
- The two of us.
So, look man.
There was a moment
you seriously ticked me off.
- Me?
- Mmm.
What was it?
Well, Kazuma, when you came swimming
toward us, I tried to high-five you.
I was like, "All right, you made it!"
But then…
you threw your whole weight on me.
I pretty much almost drowned, straight-up.
Well, I seriously held back, to be honest.
You don't need to hold back at all.
It's not about me
not needing to hold back.
It's like,
if I didn't need to hold back, you know,
I would've taken you down right there.
You should've done it then.
- You should've just done it then.
- Sorry?
If that's how you felt,
you should've done it.
If you don't back off,
I might lay you out.
Lay me out?
If you think you can do it, try me.
- Wanna go, then?
- Yeah. No, come at me, seriously.
Yeah. Yeah.
Why are you acting so calm, man?
What's your problem?
Come at me. Huh?
- Security, stop them!
- Security, where have you gone off to?
No… Don't throw hands, don't throw hands.
- Come at me.
- Hey, Maru.
- Maru, be careful.
- Chill out.
- Kazuma.
- Maru is here.
Security, hurry up!
Maru is the last person who can stop this.
Maru can't possibly stop this!
- Security, hurry up!
- Maru can't stop this!
What's wrong?
- You watch yourself.
- Right back at you.
Why is this happening?
- Oh, no, it's way late.
- Too late!
It's way late.
I could eat you for breakfast.
Oh, bring it on.
I can't wait for you to prove it.
I'll remember this.
- Hey, Kamaken.
- Do whatever you want.
Hey.
You wanna fight, just say when.
- Bring it on.
- Come with me.
I'm gonna kill that guy.
I don't care anymore.
I'll get expelled.
I said, let go of me!
Come at me, you bastard!
Hey, Kamaken.
Hey, Kamaken. Look away for a second.
- Hey, hey.
- Let's sit over here for now.
- I'm seriously ticked off, really.
- I get it.
I get it, but it's only your first day.
This is his first day? Are you kidding?
- I'm sorry, it is, isn't it?
- That's right.
Have a seat.
What's going on? Is it the alcohol?
Well, yeah.
Why were you irritated?
Me and Sara, we were chatting and started
talking about going into the ocean.
And then, well, Kazuma--
I mean, I knew he was interested in Sara.
He just…
This is the stage
where you want to chat, right?
- With who?
- With everyone.
Honestly, I don't care if I'm expelled.
There's no one I'm interested in.
Why are you being like this?
- Mmm, it's like--
- I mean, is this what you came here to do?
- You haven't even gotten to know me yet.
- Well, that's true.
You liked me at first impression, right?
Mmm.
Now I feel like "what was that?"
I mean, that's true but… But it's also--
That makes me wonder
what kind of man you are.
What's up?
We're just chatting.
You don't know what happened?
I started to get irritated,
- Did it gradually start to bubble up?
- Yeah, exactly.
You wanted him to know,
"This isn't what you think it is."
I wanna take him.
Come on, you can't. No, no, no, seriously.
Hey, hey, hey, I'm begging you.
Hey, we're both transfer students.
- It's seriously lame.
- Kamaken.
He's clumsy, for sure.
But I think he's coming to talk,
so don't lay a hand on him and just talk.
- Relax.
- I told you, I'm calm.
We're gonna try to talk.
Don't say "try to talk."
Say "we will talk."
We're back to Ethics, aren't we?
Yeah, we're back.
Show me a reality dating show!
Sorry, I'm sorry. I mean,
we want to do that too, but I apologize.
It's enough already! Seriously.
- I'm counting on you.
- Yeah, we should talk.
- Let's go, Mimi.
- Yeah.
Let's talk.
To be honest, man,
when I met you at the beginning, you know…
I genuinely thought you were a good guy.
And that's why, like…
Look, it's fine to come at me
all aggressive, but there are limits.
I apologize for that. I think I also…
Obviously, I hadn't considered
your feelings
because I was only thinking
about Sara at that time.
But, truly, I think
this goes for both of us,
but you're not gonna let any friendship
get in the way of love, right?
Well, that's true. So, you know,
amongst this group of good guys,
we can get along
except for when it comes to love,
but there'll definitely
be times when we clash,
and we talked about facing that
when it happens, right?
We agreed on that.
So, I don't know what made this so…
A big part of it is also the fact
that I almost drowned…
- For that, I'm really sorry.
- It's totally fine.
I think that was what
sort of made me reach my boiling point.
Because I was really holding back.
But, regarding that,
you don't have to hold back anymore.
- If we clash, we clash.
- Yeah, that's true.
I think that's okay.
I feel really bad about it.
I feel like I acted a little immaturely.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry too.
- Well, but from now on…
- I've calmed down.
If there happens to be
another time when we clash like this,
- I intend to face you head-on.
- That's fine by me.
And I want you
to come face me head-on too.
Did you guys work it out?
The clash between men?
Yeah.
I feel like I acted a bit immaturely.
Not entirely.
I don't think you've been--
I just mean, from now on, I don't want you
to hesitate to clash with me.
Nice ocean, huh?
Yeah.
Well, I feel really bad.
Let's fix the mood, starting now.
- As long as we face each other head-on.
- Agreed.
- Let's not hide what we're thinking.
How was the barbecue?
It was fun, getting to experience
Okinawa for the first time together.
I was so emotionally unstable today.
- Yeah, I see.
- I can't help it.
I'm starting to feel like
I don't know what to do anymore.
I told him I liked him,
and now he's acting cocky.
"Well then,
I'll go talk to somebody else."
And off he went.
He never acted like that before.
It's like, because he knows I like him,
he's going to someone else
to make me jealous.
That kind of behavior pissed me off.
You don't know it was on purpose, though.
Maybe he just genuinely
wanted to chat with everyone.
So it's all about how you interpret it.
How long are you going to keep staying
in that immature mindset?
I can't help but think
that maybe you're just insecure.
I mean the point of being here
isn't really to be mature.
I agree.
We're here to find love.
And hopefully we can, you know,
face each other while doing it.
But you're not making sense.
Like, you're not being consistent.
Why are you so condescending?
- Because you're not being consistent.
- Even if I'm not,
what makes you think you can say things
that are so condescending?
- I'm saying, you won't be liked.
- You say things like that all you want.
I'm not here to be educated by you.
And you're free not to listen.
I'm said I'm not here to be educated,
- yet you're still being condescending.
- I'm just saying, you won't be liked.
Well, it's not like I'm here to be liked.
Maybe you should make more of an effort.
It is happening all over again!
Am I in my own personal hell?
- Since last year.
- My apologies.
I come because they told me
that this is a reality dating show.
And I keep getting shown
footage like this.
I'm sorry, truly.
I'm about to lose my damn mind!